Wang Zhong bring the shelf to me
王仲 把那架子给我推过来
hurry up
马上
And the clothes props together
把服装跟道具拿过来
Let the models in
让模特进场
Shun Jia hurry up and help me choose some clothes
上顺佳 帮有我挑件欧时力的衣服
Ok help me find somewhere to tie up the donkey
行 给我找地儿挫好纹阿
Be quick let the models in
快 快 模特进场了 进场了
Oh my god there is not time for makeup hurry up
哎哟宝贝 别化了 没时间了 快点吧
Is this all right
这个好吗
It feels great
这挺有质感的
l also think this one is better
我也觉得这个好
Donkey is coming
驴来了啊
The donkey works hard
辛苦了驴
How about you
你这边怎么梯呵
Almost what do you think
差不多了 你看呢
The editor will be here soon.! will pick him up
主编马上来了 我去接
Please give the ring to the stylist
你把戒指交给造型师
This really makes us feel like farm workers
真把咱们当场工使了
Try it
旋 戴戴试试
I think the quality is very good
我觉得这成色不错
How about it
怎么样
l realise that choosing a ring is just like choosing a husband
我发现选戒指就像选老公一样
you must choose the right one
必须得选最合适的那一个
otherwise you are wasting your time
否则的话 选择不对 努力白费
Exactly
精尽
I don’t care whether you haven't slept
我才不管你睡不睡觉 跟谁睡觉
Don't even think about sleep if the publication is going to be delayed
你耽误了出版 以后就走想睡觉了
Who did this
这是谁干的 这是
Your donkey is causing a lot of trouble The editor is calling for you
你的驴问神了 主编叫你呢
How is that possible
怎么可能呢 我的驴
My donkey is working there, it is reliable"
不在那工作呢嘛 多和敬业呀
The donkey has gone
驴跑了
Help me You stepped on my shoes
哎呀 快拉我一下 踩到我的鞋了
Go and catch my donkey
抓住玄 我的驴 抓住它
In fact what happened today wasn’t my fault
其实 今天这事不是我干的
Wang Shunjia tell me if you didn’t do it who did
王顺佳 你告诉我 不是你干的是谁干的
I think the donkey is getting on your nerves
这驴是你和弄毛的吧
Do you really think we can shoot this film
这片子还能拍吗
I think you're too busy preparing for the wedding
我看你是不是忙结婚都忙晤了啊
Shun Jia Shun Jia
上顺佳 顺佳
Shun Jia
上顺佳
Stop bothering me
哎呀 你别老叫我
Sorry sorry
Sorry Sorry
Shun Jia It makes me angry
上顺佳 太气人了
Shun Jia listen to me
顺佳你听我说
Stop following me around Leave me alone
你别老跟着我
Calm down
我说你冷静点 啊
l have to explain to her
我今天必须找她说明白
Its better to be Supplements Editor than unemployed
副刊总比失业强吧
This is a cover-up
这不一手遮天嘛
There’s a financial crisis now can't you calm down
金融都危机了 你就不能淡定点
Editor you can have a look
主编 您看一下
let me see
拿来
Hello Editor
主编好
Go ahead go ahead go ahead!Stop here
再往前 往前 再往前 章车 停 这儿
The article needs to be reported by Monday
周一报选题
The editor says you are an expert on feelings and emotions
主编说你是情感专家
So he wants you to do the Relationships column this time
一定让你做这一期的两性专栏
The Relationships column
两性专栏
About the different effects of Viagra
关爱男性健康十周年
the 16 ways to become a tough guy
成为新硬汉的十六种方法
about the 8 ways to prevent suicide
防止婚变的8种绝技
and to abuse public power to take revenge against a personal enemy
公报私人呵
All our competitors are on top
我们这次的竞争对手都是最顶尖的
so the U.S. authorities are very concerned about it
所以美国总部十分重视
They have sent us an excellent designer Mia to help us out
派给我们米亚这么优秀的设计师 和合伙人来助阵
It's great Mia has arrived just in time for the bidding meeting in Hainan
这次海南竞标会 也正是因为米亚及时的赶到
Providing our team has valuable experience and strategies
提供给我们团队宝贵的经验和策略
let's hope that this project has unparalleled success
才使得这次竞标获得成功
Shun Jia I’m having a meeting now
我正在开会呢 顺佳
Its one meeting after another with you you're always in meetings
开会 又是开会 你就没有不开会的时候
You should marry your conference table
你去跟你的会议桌结婚好了
Please give me the documents of emotional type of tear
情感类催泪的都给我拿过来
The case will have to restart
才使得这个案子又起死回生
Let's see the next one
请看下一张
This project is about HaiNan International Travel
海南国际旅游岛整体规划项目
Including the design of the Island’s sights
包括岛屿景点设计
Water Ride Park
中心区水上乐园设计
restaurant service business hall, and so on"
中心区餐饮设计 商务会馆
Mia
米亚
Shun Jia
上顺佳
Shun Jia let’s split up
上顺佳 我们分手吧
LuoYi you are still alive
罗伊 你真的还活着
Wu Ju Yuan don’t give up we still have 18 days to go
吴巨源 坚抑阿 还有十八天
We can sleep together afterwards
十八天后 我们就可以睡一起了
He could go with you
让它陪你
Shun Jia
上顺佳
Cat Mummy couldn't bear to be away from you
毛毛 妈妈舍不得你
Where did you come from boy
你小子哪冒出来的 啊
You haven't been in touch with me for years
这么久不联系
It's time to get up Wu Ju Yuan
该起床了 吴巨源
Cheeky I'll give you an injection
这么不乖 我要给你打针了
First to wipe a little alcohol cotton
先抹点酒精棉
Inject your penicillin
给你来一针青霉素
Does it hurt
痛吧
I'll give you a massage
阿姨给你摸一摸
You lasted a long time today
今天挺能忍的嘛
I'll catch you again
给我抓住了
No please listen to my explanation
不是 你听我解释
Don't hit me 1 am really Wu Ju Yuan
你别打了 我真的是吴巨源
It's a typical head trauma
典型的头部外伤
that leads to thickening of the brain membrane
导致脑隔膜增厚
water in the brain
脑腔积水
and reduced blood circulation which will eventually lead to cancer
脑循环环境恶化形成癌变
The pituitary gland is under pressure and the situation will continue to worsen until the point of death
脑垂体挤压受损 继续坏死
Do you remember when you were injured
什么时候受的伤阿 还记得么
You probably didn’t realize it at the time
就你们俩不自觉
Who let you in here Go and queue
谁让你们进来的 排队去
Sorry Sorry
对不起 对不起
In 1958
五八年
his mother had just passed away
他妈妈前段时间刚去世
and his girlfriend had just split up with him after he was fired
女朋友也跟他分手了 工作又丢呼
I didn’t realize you had suffered so much
怎么那么避阿
you should have told me about it earlier
那你也早点跟我说的呵
It's all your fault I nearly lost my virginity to you
都赖你 你害人家差点失身了
Didn’t you know Shun Jia
你知不知道 知不知道 ”上顺佳
I’m sorry but what can I do now
那现在怎么办呵
Join me so that we can help him together
跟我一起帮帮他
OK
咽
Kiss me
亲一个
Shun Jia
上顺佳
If you don’t kiss me 1’ll kiss you
你不亲我 我亲你啦
We haven't even mentioned breaking up and you want to commit suicide
还没提分手就要自杀
Even now you both want to split up
你们都这个时候了 还要分手
why
你给我个理由
I'm still not marrying you why should I give you a reason
我又不是跟你结婚 给你什么理由
So tell me why did you give up college so early
那你告诉我 你大学上一半
l went to open a restaurant but it failed
跑去开和餐厅 赔了
and then I lost a lot of money on the stock market
跑去炒股 毁了
No contact for all these years why
无缘无故失踪这么多年 你给我个理由
I can't live with you any more
你们家住不了了
I'll go and stay in a hotel
我自己出去找个旅馆吧
If you have 500 yuan you can afford to move out
你现在如果能从身上 拿出五百块钱 你就出去住
Here you are you can use this
这给你 先拿着用
Junhao Zhang
张俊洗
Are you a chef Do you really enjoy cooking
你不是厨子吗 你是不是特喜欢做钢阿
Otherwise please help me
要不我让给你你来做
l hate cooking
我讨厌做饭
Here taste this
mn 到冯
Zhang Junhao
张俊洗
good morning here is your mobile phone
早啊 给你一手机
24 hours open Remember keep going
二十四小时开机呵 记住了啊 继续
Ok input power again
好 力度不够 再来 继续
Are they all girls
怎么都是女的呵
The kicking action should be merciless and fast
踢出来动作要狠 要快
I can’t do that
女的没法打
The men are arriving
男的来了
Il can’t hit a stranger
不认识我下不去手
No problem I'll introduce you
没关系 我给你介绍介绍
OK come on
好 来
What's going on That's not straight
怎么回事儿 伸不则阿
No no
嘛呢
What are you doing
干嘛呢 这这这干嘛呢这
Bark out come on! Shout like a man
喊出来知道吗 喊出来 像个爷们儿样喊出来
Ya Ya
呀 呀
I didn’t kick you you just fell over yourself
我没蹦你 你自己倒的吧
What's the matter with your leg What kind of leg is that
腿怎么回事 这什么及阿
Is this really a leg It looks like a piece of ham
你那是腿嘛 你这火邮阿
You are an adult now
这么大人了
But you don’t have any sense
一点都不动脑子
Isn't someone supposed to be taking care of you
你们有人管没 有人管没人乱阿
Who brought them in
这都谁带来的
Children the earth is a speck of dust
小朋友们 地球犹如一粒人尘埃
It takes just 8 minutes for light from the sun to reach the earth
一束光线从太阳照射到地球上 只需要八分钟
but it is 25,000 light years"
但是从太阳照射到银河系上呢
from the sun to the edge of the Milky Way
就需要2.5万光年
Does everyone understand
大家都听明白了吗
Yes
听明白了
The earth is just a speck of dust in the universe
地球在宇宙中就是一颗小尘:鞠阿
We are completely insignificant in the universe
个人在宇宙中更是微不足道
So such a small problem is really nothing
那点小小的烦恼又算什么呢
Zhang Jun Hao what are you trying to say
张俊水 你想开点吧
Teacher can I ask how many years are there in a light-year
老师 请问一光年等于几年呵
Auntie one day in the sky is equal to one year on the ground
阿姨 天上一天 地下一年
of course one light-year is equal to 365 days
一光年当然等于365年
Really So how many years are there really in a light-year
真的阿 这一光年到底等于几年"阿
A light-year is the distance that light travels in one year
光年是光走一年的距离
Oh I see
哦 这么回鄞阿
You know so much
你知道还挺多嘛
I'd like to ask you another question
我再问你一个问题阿
You told me you are a chef so why do you hate cooking
你说你是一厨师 你怎么讨厌做饭呢
You are so sloppy is it also a matter of fashion
你那么遵遇是不是也是一种时尚呢
Oh me
响 我
Hey
喂
overtime again
又加隐阿
So what time in the evening is it now
晚点是几岛阿
I don't care Wu Ju Yuan
我不管 吴巨源
We won't get married if you don’t get home before 11 o'clock
晚上十一点之前你不回家 咱俩就别结了
If can't see you every day I don't know why I should marry you
每天见不到你人 我嫁给你干嘛
Honestly do you really want to break up with Shun Jia
你是真打算跟顺佳分手啊
Leaving a woman because of another woman
我告诉俐阿 因为一个女人 离开另一个女人
It is not breaking up it is called abandoning her
不叫分手 叫抛奔
Can I ask you a question too
我能不能也问你一个问题
If
如果 我是说如果
l mean if you two break up what should you do
你们俩分手了 你会怎么办
The universe is so huge It’s the same for anyone that breaks up
宇宙那么大 离了谁还不都一样
right
对吧
Who's there
放阿
Why don't you close the door when you're taking a shower
你洗澡不关门啊
I think Shun Jia is very well
我觉得顺佳不错
What are you two doing closing the door
你们两个关着门干什么
You won't
你们不会
You can have a rinse before going out
你冲了再趟阿
I’m going to have a body scrub
我搓会儿 搓会儿
Ok
行了
Wu Junyuan don't forget to send an invitation card
吴巨源 别忘了发请帖
I’m going to get married soon
我要结婚了
What should I give you
你结婚
when you get married
我该送你点什么呢
Otherwise I’m going to pull out of this deal
要不我退出这个项目吧
The 13 ways to die for love is a really funny article
13种殉情方式 这样的文章很好玩吗
But the aim of my article is
可是我文章的意图是制止那些
To stop lovelorn people from committing suicide
制止那些失恋的人去自阔阿
It's really bad taste
拿别人的生命和感情去调侃
to laugh at others’ lives and feelings
低级趣味
That doesn't make me want to work in the warehouse
那也不至于让我看仓库吧
I think you don't appreciate your time
我看份阿 现在日子过得太舒服了
The work of a warehouse manager is too easy for you
仓库管理员的工作对你来说
I think it is very appropriate
我认为非常非常合适
And as for The 13 ways to die for love
还有有阿 我看这13种殉情方式呢
you ought to try each one
每一种你都不妨认真地去党试一下
Shun Jia
上顺佳
That's really unreasonable
简直太不可理喻了
No it’s not Didn't you know that she once tried to commit suicide because of her ex-boyfriend
不是 你没听说她曾经为前男友自杀过吗
Sister
大姐
why didn’t you tell me earlier Please tell me earlier next time
我拜托你以后能不能早点训阿
I'm come back
我回来了
It's really awful for unmarried women
女人不结婚真是可怕啊
Especially working with an unmarried editor
尤其是跟不结婚的主编在一起工作
Ah that’s
简直就是
Woo
哇
you swear you never cooked
你不折死不做饭吗
Go ahead I will charge you three months rent if you don’t cook it well
好好何阿 做不好了罚你三个月房租
Bring me red wine hurry up
快去拿红酒 快去
You won't be told will you
你不乖是不量阿
Do you believe I will put you in order after marriage in 2 days
信不信两天以后你嫁过来我收拾舍阿
Please sit down I have something to tell you
上顺佳 你坐好 我有话跟你说
What are you two doing you’re being so tender to each other
你们俩干嘛 含情脉脉的
Hurry up
旋呀你快去嘛 快去快去快去
Wait a moment let’s warm up first
等一下 来点气氛
Come on sing with us let’s warm up
旋 一起唱一唱嘛 来点气氢阿
Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday to you
Shun Jia let’s break up ok
上顺佳 我们分手吧
What
啊
What is he saying
他说什么
Let's break up ok
我们分手吧
We both aren't really suited for marriage
我们俩真的不适合结婚
This joke isn’t funny at all
你这 你这玩笑开得一点都不好笑
I'll tell you a joke
我给你们说个笑谭阿
l brought in my just-finished article to the office this morning
我今天早上拿着我新做的专题
13 Ways to Die for Love
13种殉情方式
And gave it to our chief editor to review
我去给我们主编看
Then she said Wang Shun Jia Wang Shun Jia Wang Shun Jia
然后我们主编说 王顺佳王顺佳
You really are low you know
你就是低级趣味 你知道吗
Someone like you is suitable Suitable to manage a warehouse
像你这样的人就应该去 就应该去看仓库
I think she’s really unreasonable
我觉得她简直不可理喻
Then Xiao Chi told me Don’t you know Wang Shun Jia
后来小池跟我说 说 王顺佳你知道吗
that our chief editor
我们主编以衣m阿
was abandoned by her ex-boyfriend She tried to commit suicide
就是被人家男朋友甩过 她就自杀过
so she cannot stand to hear people mention suicide
所以说她根本受不了人家 会提自杀那码子事
Jun Hao do you really want to leave
俊浩 你要趟阿
1 do want to leave
是我要走
Why didn’t you tell me until today
为什么今天才告诉我
Sorry
对不起
Zhang Jun Hao you knew about it before didn’t you
张俊水 你早就知道对不对
Go to hell
滚
Shun Jia
上顺佳
Ju Yuan
巨源
Ju Yuan Ju Yuan you can't leave
巨源 巨源 不是 你不能趟阿
If someone should go and if you must go I will
你不能起阿 要走也是我走
Please let us tidy up together then
你实在要走 你等我收拾东西咱们一起走
You can't leave now
你现在还不能走
If 1 don’t leave what am I going to do
我不能走 我待在这干什么
Jun Hao
俊少
help me to calm her down
俊少 帮有我好好安慰安慰她
How can I help you to calm her down Ju Yuan
我帮你怎么安慰她 巨源 巨
The earth is immense
地球是少瀚的
The earth appears to be huge but compared to the universe it's tiny
整个宇宙在地球中显得是
The earth is too small in the universe
整个地球 一个地球在整个宇宙中 显得是那么的微小
Looks like a speck of dust
简直就像是一颗人尘埃
So people are even smaller
你想一个人 在地球上那更是显得微小
Therefore forget your worrying it won't be missed
他更可以没有烦恼 更可以去忽略
Right
对不对
Light-year
光年
is light light
光年就是光 听 光
l
我
wanna
要
get
结
married
婚
Are those you two
这照片是你们俩人吗
Divorced or married if you're married you sit closer together
离婚还结婚呐 结婚坐近点
Wang Shun Jia are you crazy
王顺佳 你是不是疯了
Do you think you can get back at me this way
你以为你这样子就是在报复我吗
I must be crazy
我就是疯了
It's not just because of the marriage no matter who he is
不就是结婚嘛 跟谁结不是结阿
Wu Ju Yuan let me tell you
吴巨源 我告诉你
I don’t have to have you to get married
没有俐阿 我一样能把这个婚给结了
Shun Jia
上顺佳
Shall we eat now
吃吗
Shun Jia are you still using that knife
上顺佳 你那把刀还用吗
Who's there What are you doing Come down now
放阿 干什么的 赶紧下来 赶紧下来
Quickly
快点
Quickly come down now
别看了 下来 赶紧下来
You're Zhang Jun Hao
你叫张俊洗
and you’re Wang Shun Jia
你叫王顺佳
didn’t you get married yesterday
这不昨天刚结的婚吗
Everything is hard at the beginning young man
万事开头难 小伙子
Take care
保重吧
You can go now
回吧
You’re mad
神经病
No you’re mad
你神经病
l heard there are many definitions of fashion
我听过无数种有关时尚的定义啊
What does being fashionable mean
那时尚到底是什么
Being fashionable is probably an attitude to life
简单的说 时尚她也许是一种生活的态度
Shun Jia
上顺佳
Shangbie Du the global artistic director is going to give a lecture Come quickly with me
全球艺术总监杜尚别来讲课了 赶紧跟我走
lam only a warehouse worker why should I listen to him
我一死看仓库的 我听他干呈阿
No he is a great master and we should respect him Hurry up hurry up
不行 那是大师必须瞻仰 赶紧赶紧赶紧
don't loiter Come on come on
墨墨迹迹的 走走走 走
For example if you can distinguish between the different years of the classic LV styles
你如果能分辨认LV 不同年代的经典款
you are very fashionable
你就很时尚
But if you wear an LV style to participate in a primary school alumni association
可是如果你穿着任何一新-V 去参加小学校友会
you are not very fashionable
你就很不时尚
If you can tell the difference
如果你能看得出来
In his mind David Beckham is Victoria's eldest son
贝克汉姆在心理上 其实他是维多利亚的长子
you aren't fashionable
你就很时尚
Otherwise if you are going to count the number of wrinkles for Victoria instead of Backham
可是如果你去替贝克汉姆 数维多利亚脸上的煞纹
you aren't fashionable Can I say it like this OK
你就不时尚
I don't know if it is very fashionable
不知道像我这种 刚被别人甩
that was abandoned by one man
二十四小时之内又嫁给了别人
and then got married to another within 24 hours
算不算是一种时尚
Of course
当然很时尚
it is fashionable and it is much more fashionable than crying for 24 hours
比被甩后连哭二十四小时时尚
l have been married six times
我结过六次婚
and now I’m 60 years old and still single
我今年六十岁 现在还单身
Maybe a lot of people think that l am very fashionable
也许有很多人认为我很时尚
but every time I went through a divorce
可是在我经历每一次离婚的时候
My heart felt like it had been taken out
我的心脚阿 就像要被摘掉一样
That's so strange
想想真的很奇怪
You see I work at the bottom
你说我工作在最底层
You have just been abandoned
刚被人甩了
and then you jump into the fiery pit again
还主动跳进火坑
But my heart is tired
可是我的心疲倦
But why don't I feel sad
可为什么我一点都不感觉到悲伤呢
I don't even have the strength to cry
我连恬的力量都没有
l even want to laugh
甚至还想笑
Is that fashionable
这样算时尚吗
Let me tell you
我跟你训阿 你现砷阿
you are in the numb phase where you
经历的是习侈期 麻木不仁
you don’t realize what has happened
还没有意识到事情已经发生了
Then it is the anger phase
接着呢 是喷发期
the feeling of pain increases
痛苦的感觉急剧攀升
and you will enter a suffering phase
然后你将进入痛楚期
also called the plateau phase
又叫做平台期
a dull stuggling feeling
隐隐作痛的感觉始终纠缠
until death or until rebirth
直到死去 或者新生
Sorry
对不超阿
we have gone beyond the scope of fashion with this conversation
刚刚讲的那个时尚已经超越范围了
So when you judge everything by fashion You are not fashionable
所以 当你拿时尚来判断一切 你就很不时尚
Taste it slowly
慢慢品味吧阿
Cheers
请各位喝香槟
Have a look let's go
看看去 走
This is the new champagne from the French Pommery wine makers
这是来自法国ommery 酒厂的最新香槟
let's taste it
请大家来试试看 来
What do you think
感觉怎么样
It's quite special
挺特别的
It looks like a wedding veil
有一种婚纱的味道
What's wrong
怎么回事
What's the matter with you
怎么回鄞阿你
Are you okay
哎呀 行不行阿
Ha
行不行
Shun Jia what’s wrong with you
上顺佳 你又怎么了
Are you playing your strange tricks on us again
你又想摘什么怪
No I will not! I’m stuffed
不是 不是 哈着了
What's up
怎么啦
Why are the rims of your eyes all red
怎么眼眶都红了
I didn’t think that the champagne could also move me
没想到香槟也能让人动情
and make me cry
产生催泪的作用
I think you are a very sensitive person
我想你应该是一个很敏感的人
you can tell that
你还可以捕捉得到
this wine is also one of the elements of feelings
这酒也是感情的元素之一啊
Is she your editor
她是你编辑吗
Oh yes
哦 是
lam going to ask come up with a main theme for the sequel in next issue
我正在让她做下期的主题
It's going to be about feelings and emotions
是关于情感的
Ok
好
I’m looking forward to reading that article
我等着看你专题阿
Are you ok
你行不行阿
Shun Jia did you hear that
上顺佳 听见没有
You have to come up with the main theme of the article in the next issue
下期让你做专题呢
Here’s your big chance
机会来了
Why do I always manage to lose face at these occasions
我怎么在什么场合都那么丢人了呢
No didn’t the expert just say
别 大师不刚说完吗
that feelings are more important than fashion
感情大于时尚
Why
为什么呀
What have I got for people to look at
我有什么好看的呀
"Your cousin brother or grandmother will all come to see, do we need to go this far"
你七大姑八大姨都得来 至于吗
Besides we're not being honest are we
再说咱们俩也不是来真的阿 对不对
Once they've seen us we can get a divorce
他们看过以后 咱俩就可以离婚了
Now can you tell me how long they will stay
那我能知道一下他们住多久吗
Just two or three months
也就两三个月吧
Two or three
两三个
In fact there is another way
其实还有个别的办法
Come on smile! Isn’t she the woman you love most in the world
来 笑一笑 这不是你最爱的女人吗
That looks great just relax and hold it there
对 放松一点
Can you communicate with each other please
要有交流
Okay you both need to communicate Communicate by eye contact
好的 两个人交流 眼神的交流
Girl look at your husband Come on smile please
姑娘看老公 来笑一个
Look over there
看那边
Good you look like you’re longing for a perfect future
误 好 尽慢美好的未来
Make your fingers into an orchid shape and point over there
兰花指 指着那边
Good beautiful
好 漂亮
Can you tilt down the board a little
哎呀 板 低一点 好
Prince and Princess try to make it look like you’re running
王子与公主找一种奔跑的感郑阿
Hold hands running swing your hair up and around
手拉着手 奔跑起来 把头发甩起来
Can you see that bird’s nest
有没有看到那个乌离
Right you need that type of “hey” expression in your eyes
对 那个眼神要那种旋的感间阿
Good come on Nice be aware of your eyes
好 来来来 好 注意眼神
You must have the dynamic feeling of running
一定要奔跑 要动感
Look your running is making me feel hot
你看 把我都给跑热了
Come come over here
来 快
The key of this pose is in your eyes
这个pose 关键看你们的眼神
This type of eye expression usually has two levels of meaning
这种眼神通常有两层含义
One is deep hate
一个 恨得太深
and the other is burning love
还有一种就是爱的太切
Get ready
来 准备了啊
Goodbye Bye bye
再见 “拜拜
Xiao Jiang are you here yet
小藉 到了吗
Boss I’ve already photographed that for you
老大 我 我已经蔡你拍了
You've done it again
你 又干这种事
You can go on sleeping
您接着睡吧
I’m going to buy some ice-cream
我去买点冰激凌
This is tonight’s special relationships program
亲爱的听父朋友 这里是新硬汉两性专栏
and our topic tonight
今晚 我们的话题是
is the 10th anniversary special issue about Men’s Health
男性健康10周年特别专题
Every man needs to be a tough guy
每个男人都应该是新硬汉
The new tough guy is not only strong
新硬汉不仅是身材健硕
but also should know about caring
更重要的是需要懂得关心
Get up Begin your painful life now
起床啦 开始隐隐作痛的生活吧
The magazine will stop receiving articles the day after tomorrow Don’t forget the special column about newlyweds
杂志后天截稿 新婚专栏你别忘了啊
En
咽
Please look forward to
敏请期待
NanShang that will wake up for the desire of love
男冀 唤醒我们对爱的欲望
Thank you
谢谢
Orgasm
高潮
you have a fake marriage don’t you
你不假结婚吗
Other people will hate you you know that don’t you
你这样会被人恨死的 你知不知道
More than 70% of women have not experienced an orgasm
全球70% 以上的女性都没体验过高潮
So you need help
所以才需要 引导
Why aren't you a chef anymore You're good at cooking
你做饭那么好吃 为什么不做厨师了
Did you try Tom Pizza It's very delicious
你吃过汤姆饼吗 特别的好吃
My dad was a pastry chef before
以前我区是个糕点师
and he was best at making something called Tom Pizza
他最擅长的就是做一种叫汤姆饼的东西
One day my dad and a young waitress that worked in their restaurant
有一天 我区和他们餐厅的 一个年轻的女服务员
was about the same as this one and he took me to have a ride on the merry-go-round in the park
带我去公园坐旋转木马 就跟这差不多
l was really happy at the time
我特别高兴
When I was playing my dad suddenly asked me
我玩着玩着 我区就突然问我
whether I was willing to let that waitress be my mother
说 愿不愿意那个女服务员做我妈妈
Later on my dad bought me enough tickets for me to ride on the merry-go-round for the whole day
后来我爸给我买了 我够坐一整天旋转木马的票
Then gave me back a Tom Pizza
还给了我一袋汤姆饼
As I grew up I gradually came to understand
慢慢我长大了 才知道
about that day with my dad and that young waitress
那天 我区和那年轻的服务员
He ran away
跑啦
No way that’s terrible
真该死
My mum fell in love with my dad because of Tom Pizza
我妈是因为汤姆饼爱上我区的
but I ate the last few pieces of Tom Pizza that my dad gave to my mum
而我吃光了我区给我妈最后的几个汤姆饼
Many years passed
很多年过去了
my mum still couldn't stop thinking about Tom Pizza so I was wondering whether I could make it
我妈依然对汤姆饼念念不忘的
So I went to work as a cook even though l hadn’t yet graduated from university
于是我大学没毕业 我就去当了厨子
But I didn't work at Tom Pizza
可是直到我妈走的那一天
until after my mum had passed away
我也没有把汤姆饼做出来
This is the HaoxiShi Wedding online-service-Shop
您好 喜事网客服中心
Your wedding dress is finished
您订的桂由美婚纱已经做好了
Wedding Shop
婚纱
My husband died
老公死了
Sorry Sorry
对不起 对不超阿
Shun Jia This is
上顺佳 这位就是
Are you Miss Wang Shun Jia
这位就是王顺佳小姐是吧
Yes hello Hello
对对对 你好 你好你好你好
Here is my business card Thanks
这是我的名片 ”好好
here’s mine
这是我的
It is true that what a man writes reflects his personality
真是文如其人啊
“The Sweet Smell of Success” is the name of our company
活色生香既是我们的公司名字
It is also one of our core values
也是我们的价值理念
l like to have a cultural platform to convey this cultural concept
我一直在找一个文化平台 能来传递这种理念
It wasn’t until 1 read your articles
直到看到你的文章
Your work is rich and full of flavor like a sumptuous feast
你的文章就像是一顿大餐
it is lively but not too strong and colorful yet not flashy
但是却活而不腻 色而不艳
It's almost
这简直就是一种
a state of mind
境界
Can I have a word
一句话
Manager Zhou just wants to support our special supplement
周总就是想赞助我们的专栏
That's great news such a famous entrepreneur and company as Manager Zhou
像周总这么有品味的企业家和公司
We would be honored
我们欢迎
This is what we propose
我们倡导的
What we propose is limited distribution and release
我们倡导的是收放有度的
What we propose is a talented and elegant image
我们倡导的是收放有度的俊和雅
What do you mean
你到底想干嘛
Please come and collect your wedding photos
你们的结婚照寄到我这了
when it is convenient for you
其实俊浩这人不错 我觉得
In my eyes you are a real idiot
我觉得你就是个混蛋
Here you are
给
She said that these wedding pictures were taken for her parents
她说这个婚纱是拍给她获妈看的
I Know she told me
我知道 她跟我说过
We believe in the existence of miracles
我们相信 才会存在
Love beyond death
死了都要爱
Do not wail unless you are through
不淋漓尽致不痛快
Feelings are strong it's the only way to unburden
感情多深 只有这样才足够表白
Love beyond death
死了都要爱
Don't wail unless weep till smile
不器到微笑不痛快
Universe is destroyed heart is still
宇宙毁灭心还在
She brandishes the banners of love
她扬起爱情胜利的旗帜
You want me to choose the way of loving you
你要我选择继续爱你的方式
Shun Jia don’t go off singing
上顺佳 别唱了 走吧
look there’s no one here to see everyone has gone now Stop it
你看人都没了 都走光了 别唱了
Editor Chi have fun
池编辑 玩儿嘛 玩儿就玩儿得开心点
Yep I will go with you and take editor Wang back home
是吧 今天奉陪到底 负责送王编辑回家
Jun Hao
俊少
oh no This is Xiao Chi
喂 不是 我是小池
we we are singing now
啊 我们唱歌呢
can you come over
你要不要一起唱阿
Shun Jia is drunk
你们家顺佳早就喝高了
I'd prefer to give up in the morning
宁愿清醒忍痛地放弃你
It's hard to know that
太委屈
I'm the last person to find out we broke up
连分手也是让我最后得到消息
Don't cry
不哭泣
because ! don’t owe you anything
因为我对情对爱全都不曾亏欠你
Too sad
太委屈
you hugged another person while I am in love with you
还爱着你你却把别人拥在怀里
Hi
隆
Do you have fun
玩得开心吗
Nice thanks
很好 谢谢
Hi how are you
降 嗨 你好
Long time no see Yes
好久没见你了          蕙阿是阿
I will see you soon ok
一会去找俐阿         好的
Welcome
欢i阿
Hi Cheers
Hi Cheers
Hi How are you
Hi How are you
how are you
降 你好
Cheers
Cheers
Xiao Chi
小池
where is Shun Jia
上顺佳呢
She was here just now
刚才还在呢
My goodness
坏了
What's the matter
怎么了
Zhou Shi Hou is a sex maniac
那周世活是一色狼
No No
不是不是
No
不是
sorry Could you have a look if there is an exit
对不起 ”你看看那边有没有出口
What can I do for you Sir Nothing I know one of his friends
您需要什么帮助吗 没事 我认识 我认识
You'd better open your window Can you open your car window please
你能把这窗择下来
Excuse me sir Could you put the window down put it down
先生你让一下 窗户择下来行不行 把窗户择下来
oh Sir e sir
先生 放 先生
What are you doing
干嘛呢伤阿
No let me have a look
不是 我看看
Is he crazy
有病吧他
Calm down Calm down
您别冲动 您别冲动
Sir it’s ok it’s ok
先生算了 算了 先生
Are you crazy
有病吧你
Hey what’s going on
嘿 怎么了这是 怎么回事
Don't do this
别这样 别这样
No I’m not smashing your glass
不是 我不是要砸你玻璃
No I’m looking for my friend
不是 我是找我朋友
Looking for your friend Why did you smash my car
你找你朋友你砸我车
I told you put your window down so I could just have a look
我跟你说了 你把玻璃择下来我看一眼就行了
That's bullshit ok I’m waiting
我也下跟你废话 等着 等着你
Sir sir sir
先生 先生 先生
What you are doing Do you need to go this far
你干嘛 至于吗
Zhang Jun Hao
张俊洗
Haven't I already explained it to you
我不都跟你解释过了嘛
I don’t need your explanation
不用跟我解释
This is all thanks to our fake marriage
幸亏我们是假的
l like being cheated on
我不适合戴绿帽子
What you are saying
你说什么呢
I think I worry far too much
我觉得我的担心特别的多余
You enjoyed that didn’t you
你还玩得挺更 对吗
Yes I'm really happy But its none of your business
是挺钢阿 关你什么事
It's none of my business
不关我的事
I just want to tell you Wang Shun Jia
我就是想告诉你王顺佳
as a woman you should have a bit more self-respect
做女人还是自重一点
We just got divorced
这两天把婚离了吧
I don’t want to get involved in that monkey business with you again
我不想再跟你胡闹下去了
I should have never spent any time with you in the first place
从一开始我就不应该掺合进来
My girl
小妞
I’m coming
来了
What do you mean
什么意思呵
Do you think I’ve changed
你没发现我有什么变化
Have you put on weight
变胖了
Beat you
抽价阿
The magazine needs the draft tomorrow don’t you know
明儿杂志社交稿 你知不知道
Everyone in the world is waiting for you
全世界都在找你
Why are they waiting for me I won't do it
找我干嘛 我不干
I noticed that as soon as Jun Hao left you not only didn’t show up for a few days
我发现俊消一走 你几天不露面不说
but you also became slack in your work
还消极怠工
Have you fallen in love with him
你爱上他了
"lL can confirm 1,000% that he likes you"
我敢百分之一千地确定 他喜欢上你了
This is so annoying
烦了啊
Right
好好好
Look
看
Did you buy it yourself
自己买的
No
什么啊
Du Shang Bie has proposed marriage to me
杜尚别 向我求婚了
Really
真的假的
Of course it’s true
当然真的了
If you offer me dinner so when I am eating
请我吃饭 结果吃着吃着
he suddenly showed me a diamond ring with nine diamonds in it
突然变出一九钻钻戒
and told me he had fallen in love with me
说他爱上我了
So I said ok
然后我说行 这戒指我先收着
but first ! would check to see whether this diamond ring was real
回去验验是真是假
and then I would confirm whether or not Il agreed with his proposal
然后再确定答不答应
Have you really thought about this He has already been divorced six times
你想好了 他已经离过六次了
Do you want to be the seventh one
你想成为第七个
lam ready
我早就想好了
l have even asked my lawyer to draw up the prenuptial agreement
连婚前协议我都让律师拟好了
Once he finds the eighth one all his assets will belong to me
一旦他找第八个 所有财产全部归我所有
There are no words in this world I have no words to say in such a world
史哟 这个世界真是让我无谭阿
Beautiful
谣阿
You really like it right
特喜欢是吧
You can get Zhang Jun Hao to buy one for you
让张俊水给你补一个呵
lam going to get divorced from Zhang Jun Hao tomorrow afternoon
没机会啦 明天下午我就和张俊水离婚去
Ah
啊
Both sides are willing and there is no dispute over the assets
双方自愿 还没财产纠纷
but why do you want to divorce
那你们俩 为什么离寻阿
What do you two think Have you thought it over carefully
怎么样二位 想好了吗
Don't cry
别呈了 别哭了
Both of you if Il stamp this document
二位 我要往这上面一盖章
you two will be divorced
你们俩可就离啦
Don't cry girl
别美了姑娘
If you’re not sure about it you can go home to think about it first
有什么事呵 回家再琢磨琢磨
Don't cry don’t cry
别美了 别吴了 啊
Here you are
给
What
什么啊
Didn’t you say you wanted to eat some Tom Pizza
你不是说想吃汤姆饼吗
You managed to make it
你做出来啦
It probably won't taste the same as your dad’s
味道可能不太一样
but I think you'll like it
但对付你够了
Is it delicious
好吃吗
How does it taste I think l should apologize
就当是道交吧
Apologize for what
道什么半
What I said to you that day was too harsh
那天说你那些话有点重
l have forgotten about it
我都忘了
Do you still want to divorce
还离吗
Go home and think it over
回家江阿 再好好想想吧 给
Thanks elder sister
谢谢大姐
Is it delicious
好吃吗
Just so so
一般般
Beautiful this is a real candlelit dinner
北阿 这才是烛光晚餐呢
I think it’s a bonfire party
啊 我以为是敌火晚会呢
Stick stick tiger Stick stick stick
棒子棒子老虎 棒子棒子棒子
Stick stick insect Stick Stick chicken
棒子棒子虫 棒子棒子鸡
You
你
Stick stick chicken Stick stick tiger
棒子棒子鸡 棒子棒子老虎
Open your mouth
大口一点
My mouth is bigger than yours
我只比你大
You dare to compare yourself with me
你敢跟我比吗 你敢跟我比吗
Backstroke breaststroke crawl
蛙泳呵蛙泳 仰溯阿仰泳
Backstroke breaststroke
自由泳阿自由泳 仰泳阿卯泳
Backstroke crawl
蛙泳 仰泳
You lose You have been defeated
你输了 你输了
Ok so I lose! You say
输就输 你说
This is risky
大冒险 赶紧大冒险
Promise me you won't laugh
你不许笑
I don’t think you need to act like a gorilla
我觉得你根本不用演大猩猩
You are a gorilla
你就是一只大猩猩
The gorilla has beaten you It has nothing to do with me
大猩猩打的 不关我的事
Continue
继绰阿
Backstroke backstroke Backstroke backstroke
仰泳阿仰泳 自由泳呵自由泳
You're not allowed to lie
不许说假语阿
If you lie your whole family will die
说假话全家和死光光
Zhang Jun Hao how old were you when you stopped wetting your bed
张俊水 你几岁不尿床
Twelve
12岁
Twelve I haven’t wet my bed since I was ten years old
12岁 我10岁就不尿了
Zhang Jun Hao how old were you when you first kissed a girl
张俊消 你第一次亲女孩噶几岁啊
l was in grade 6 in primary school
小学六年级
That’s lame
太逊了
Il had my first kiss when I was in grade 3 in primary school
我小学三年级就没有初吻了
Zhang Jun Hao do you still like her
张俊水 那你现在还喜欢她吗
No
不喜欢
Zhang Jun Hao so what about you now
张俊消 那你
and then you will ask the fourth question
哎 你接下来问的是第四个问题
Let's continue with the next round ok
咱们下一轮好不好
Backstroke crawl
仰沪阿仰泳
You lose again
你又输了
Go on keep on asking questions
你接着问 接着问
So who you like now
那你现在喜欢放阿
Brother and sister do you have any social morals What's the time now
大哥大姐 有没有公德心啊
What's the time now The others have to work tomorrow
都几点了 人家明天还上班呢
Can you lower your voice
你们能不能小点硼阿
Sorry sorry
对不起 对不起
Sorry
对不超阿
It's late I have to go now
差不多了 我也该走了
Come here
来
I wish you happiness
祝你幸福
The same to you
你也一梯呵
Is there anyone
有人管没人智阿 这怎么回事这个
Who brought them in
这都谁带来的
l want to get married
我要结婚
This is Chinamobile Service for you
这里是中国移动秘书台为您服务
Leave your message
有事请留言
Shun Jia This is Jun Hao
上顺佳 我是俊洗
Are you all right
你还好吗
It was not easy the last time and it was raining
上次好不容易见一次 还下那么大的雨
so if you are free
那什么 你要是不忙的话
can we meet up once more
我们再见一面吧
Thank you
谢谢
You are welcome
不客气
What are you doing
你来干什么
Shun Jia I’m going to go now
上顺佳 我要走了
What does it have to do with me
跟我有关系吗
I promised that
我曾经答应过你
l would take you to the top of this hill to see the city
带你去山顶看这个城市
But it never comes true
可是一直没有兑现
Ok but I don’t need to do that
行了 我不需要
Shun Jia don't be like that
上顺佳 别这样
We shouldn't be enemies
我们总不该成为仇人吧
please give me a chance ok
给我个机会解释好吗
After all you are the sweetest person in this city
毕竟 你还是我在这个城市里最亲的人
Forever
永远都是
Ok I hope you can find a new sweetheart soon
那就祝你新婚愉快吧
I've got something to do and I must go now
我还有事 我先走了
Please give me your car keys You've been drinking
把车钥匙给我吧 你喝酒了
Shun Jia
上顺佳
I just hope you won't hate me
我只希望你别恨我
Go home now Your wife is waiting for you
赶紧回家吧 老婆在家等你呢
Shun Jia
上顺佳
What are you doing
到底想干什么你
Sorry
对不起
You want me to cry right To be sad with you
你想让我哭是吗 陪你伤感一下
Then you can get married tomorrow and be very happy
然后你心满意足的明天去结婚
You misunderstand me I don’t mean that at all
你误会了 我不是这个意思
Wu Ju Yuan you are really bad you know
吴巨源你就是个混蛋 你知道吗
Slowly
你慢点
Are you looking for Zhang Jun Hao
你是找张俊浩吗
Yes where is he
对 他人呢
He has left
他走了
but he asked me to give you this
他让我把这个还给你
Zhang Jun Hao I’m giving you a mobile phone
张俊少 给你一手机
Please keep it on 24 hours a day Can you remember to do that
二十四小时开机呵 记住了啊
Ok
好
Kiss me kiss me
亲一个 亲一个
One more
再来一个
Ok one more
好 我们听你的 再来一个
Now let’s cheers
那我们现在举杯
We wish they would be
我们祝福这对新人能够
happy forever
永远的幸福甜密
Thanks
谢谢
Thanks everyone cheers
谢谢 谢谢各位 Cheer
Thanks to beauty
两位美女辛苦啦
No No it’s ok
没有 没有
Do you want to eat something
去吃点东西
Who gave that to you
这谁送的
I don’t know
不知道
What are you doing
干嘛呢妞
Pretending to be a lady
装淑女呐
Ok I will introduce a handsome man to you Come on
走走 给你介绍帅哥 走走
I’m a married woman it doesn’t work on me
我一已婚妇女 介绍什么都白搭
How about next week I’ve arranged two presentations to you
下周呢 我给你安排了两个演讲
We're looking forward to it
大家都非常期待
Please don't do this
别别别
l have promised Chi that I would bring her somewhere for our honeymoon
我答应小池了 要带她去度密月
If we weren't going we would come
如果去不了的话 那就会这样
Shun Jia
上顺佳
so
怎么样
Did this champagne Pommery make you burst into tears
这条Pommery 香槟 没俱下你的眼泪呵
Ido know anything about champagne
其实我根本就不懂香槟
Oh I see
响 我懂了
l understand
我知道了
This is a kind of handmade wine from my hometown
在我老家 有一种自酿的土酒
that is not rare but
算不上名贵 但喝了之后
it is unforgettable when you drink it
肯定让你难忘
But there is not much produced
但它产量相当低
you must wait a long time
喝了之后呢 必须要再等一年
Before you could get some again
你才能再喝到它
One year It’s too long
一年呐 那还不得急死
That's it
就量阿
I will bake delicious Tom Pizza for Shun Jia 's birthday
下月顺佳生日 送她最美味的汤姆饼
Ladies and Gentleman welcome
先生小姐 你们好
This is the latest style of Tom Pizza please try it
这是我们店新推出的汤姆饼 请你们品尝一下
Ok Thanks a lot
好 谢谢阿
Hi try it
您好 欢迎品尝汤姆饼
Thank you very much
谢谢
Is it nice
好吃吗
Delicious
好吃
thanks
好 谢谢
Last month it was my dear Du’s 60th birthday aniversary
上个月我们家老村60大寿
l went back to the United States with him
我跟他回了趟美国
his daughters all came even though they were born from different mothers
他那几个不同的妈生的女儿全来了
The party was so lively
放眼望去 那叫一个热闲
Black
黑皮肤的
white
白皮肤的
. asian
黄皮肤的
all of them In this family called “Let the world lived with love”
全了        你们家这叫让世界充满爱
You are right
是阿
Sorry excuse me
对不起 打捞了
This is our new dessert Try it please
这是我们店新推出的糕点 请品尝一下
Thanks
谢谢
You are welcome
不客气
Waiter
服务员
Can I help you
怎么了
who made it
你们这西点谁做的阿
That is a new product
这是我们店新配送的
do you have the address of that
配送的盒子上有那个店的地址吗
Yes we have
有的
Excuse me could you hold it please
麻烦你拿一下
Yes thanks
好的”谢谢阿
Miss
小姐
Thanks a lot you are welcome
谢谢 不客气
Chi I have to go please pay the bill
小池 我有事我先走了 你买单呵
mad
神神叫叫的
Excuse me Miss It’s time to close
不好意思 小姐 我们要下班了
could you allow me to play one last time
我能再坐最后一轮吗
All right last one
好吧 就坐最后一侈阿
Thank you so much
谢谢
Oh you two again
还是你们两个呀
Do you really want to get a divorce
还真的要疯阿
Yes
一一 疝
Why do you want to get a divorce so much
干嘛非得讽阿
If we don’t get divorced how can we start again
不高怎么重新开罗阿
l have never enjoyed the feeling of being chased by you
我还没享受过被你追求的过程呢